Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Within the College
  - Tucker, Edward B. — Biology Department, 1981 (Folder 19.30)
  - Tenured Members of biology Department, 1981 (Folder 19.31)
  - Rejected Applications — Mellon Fund, 1979 (Folder 19.32)
  - Stokes, Alison, 1986 (Folder 19.33)
  - Alison Stokes, 1983-1986 (Folder 19.34)
  - General Office Materials — Loose, 1981-1987 (Folders 20.1-20.7)
  - Faculty Handbook: 1978-1979 (Folder 20.8)
  - Chairmen’s Handbook: 1977-1978 (Folder 20.9)
  - Academic Advisor’s Handbook — Mrs. Marla O. Mackenzie, 1977 (Folder 20.10)
  - Directory, 1977 (Folder 20.11)
  - [Student] — Appeal (Extremely Confidential), 1988 (Folder 20.12)
  - [Student] — Appeal (Confidential), 1987 (Folder 20.13)
  - [Student] — Appeal (Confidential), 1986 (Folder 20.14)
  - [Student] Appeal (Confidential), 1986 (Folder 20.15)
  - [Student] Materials (Confidential), 1986 (Folder 20.16)
  - Winter Weekend, 1987 (Folder 20.17)
  - Winter Weekend, 1985 (Folder 20.18)
  - Winter Weekend, 1984 (Folder 20.19)
  - Winter Weekend, 1986 (Folder 20.20)
  - President’s Speech/Interview, 1984 (Folder 20.21)
  - Serenading, 1987 (Folder 20.22)
  - Serenading, 1983 (Folder 20.23)
  - Senior Receptions, 1983 (Folder 20.24)
  - Senior Survey, 1985 (Folder 20.25)
  - Miscellany News, 1983-1984 (Folder 20.26)
  - Misc — Correspondence, 1988 (Folder 20.27)
  - Minority Student Roster, 1984 (Folder 20.28)
  - Madrigal Singers Tour, Mar 1985 (Folder 20.29)
  - Curry, Michele — Study in England (Confidential), 1985 (Folder 20.30)
  - Junior Year Abroad and Majors Statistics, 1985-1986 (Folder 20.31)
  - Jewish Student Complaint, 1979-1986 (Folder 20.32)
  - New Student Orientation and Freshman Parents’ Weekend, 1984 (Folder 20.33)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1983 (Folder 20.34)
  - Freshmen Orientation, 1982 (Folder 20.35)
  - Founder’s Day, 1983-1984 (Folder 20.36)
  - Founder’s Day, 1980-1982 (Folder 20.37)
  - Freshman Assembly — President Smith’s Remarks, Aug 1985 (Folder 20.38)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1986 (Folder 20.39)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1985 (Folder 20.40)
  - Freshman Orientation, 1985 (Folder 20.41)
  - Brunches in the Dorms, 1983 (Folder 20.42)
- Series V. Associations
  - AERA — American Education Research Association, 1978 (Folder 20.43)
  - AAC — Association of American Colleges, 1979-1981 (Folder 20.44)
  - AAC — Board Retreat, Mar 1982 (Folder 21.1)
  - AAC — National Conference on Liberal Learning, 1981-1982 (Folder 21.2)
  - AAC — Loose Materials, 1979 (Folder 21.3)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1978-1979 (Folder 21.4)
  - AAC Board Meeting, Sep 1981 (Folder 21.5)
  - AAC Foundation News Article, 1981 (Folder 21.6)
  - AAC — Ad-Hoc General Education Committee, 1978 (Folder 21.7)
  - AAC — Committee on liberal Learning, 1980 (Folder 21.8)
  - AAC — Commission on Curriculum and Faculty Development, 1979-1980 (Folder 21.9)
  - AAC — Commission on National Affairs, 1980 (Folder 21.10)
  - AAC — Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Folder 21.11)
  - AAC — Expense Statements (Folder 21.12)
  - AAC — Quill Quality in Liberal Learning, 1978-1980 (Folder 21.13)
  - Quill (Martin Ringle), 1980 (Folder 21.14)
  - Winton Manning, 1982-1984 (Folder 21.15)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1981-1982 (Folder 21.16)
  - ACE — Newsletter — Higher Education and National Affairs, 1976-1978 (Folder 21.17)
  - Leadership Vitality Project — Miami University, 1979 (Folder 21.18)
  - Museums Collaboration, Inc., 1978-1979 (Folder 21.19)
  - Standing Committee on Research and Development, Dec 1979 (Folder 21.20)
  - Higher Education — Long Range Planning Group, 1980 (Folder 21.21)
  - CFAT — Purpose of Higher Education, 1980 (Folder 21.22)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching — Special Seminar, Sep 17, 1981 (Folder 21.23)
  - CASE — Council for Advancement and Support of Education, 1980-1981 (Folder 21.24)
  - CAEL — Council for the Advancement of Experimental Learning, 1979-1981 (Folder 21.25)
  - FIPSE — Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education, 1978-1982 (Folder 21.26)
  - FIPSE — Tenth Anniversary, Mar 27, 1983 (Folder 21.27)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1976-1983 (Folder 21.28)
  - Carnegie Foundation Meeting, Nominating and 75th Anniversary, Goals and Purpose, 1980 (Folder 21.29)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1979-1980 (Folder 21.30)
  - Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching Trustees Meeting, Apr 4, 1981 (Folder 21.31)
  - Future Structure of the AAC, 1983-1985 (Folder 21.32)
  - AAC Report, 1985 (Folder 21.33)
  - AAC Meeting — Washington, DC, Sep 1982 (Folder 21.34)
  - AAC Meeting — Washington, DC, Sep 1983 (Folder 21.35)
  - AAC Annual Meeting — Washington, DC, Jan 1983 (Folder 22.1)
  - AAC Spring Retreat, Apr 1983 (Folder 22.2)
  - AAC — Harpers Ferry, West Virginia, Apr 1981 (Folder 22.3)
  - College of New Rochelle, 1979-1980 (Folder 22.4)
  - Carnegie Council on Policy Studies in Higher Education, 1978-1979 (Folder 22.5)
  - CFAT Board Meeting — Washington, DC, Nov 1983 (Folder 22.6)
  - AAC Conference — Denver, Jan 1981 (Folder 22.7)
  - AAC/Project on Understanding of Liberal Learning, 1981 (Folder 22.8)
  - AAC/Women’s Equity Committee, 1982-1983 (Folder 22.9)
  - AAC Review Committee, Apr 1985 (Folder 22.10)
  - AAC — Council Oversight Committee, Nov 1983 (Folder 22.11)
  - AAC Annual Meeting — Washington, DC, Feb 1985 (Folder 22.12)
  - AAC — 72nd Annual Meeting, Jan 1986 (Folder 22.13)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1983-1985 (Folder 22.14)
  - National Meditation Panel, 1984 (Folder 22.15)
  - AAC — Loose Materials, 1982-1983 (Folder 22.16)
  - AAC Annual Meeting, Jan 1982 (Folder 22.17)
  - Association of American Colleges Meeting, Mar 1981 (Folder 22.18)
  - AAC/CILE (Council for the Improvement of Liberal Education, 1983 (Folder 22.19)
  - AAC — Loose Files, 1981-1982 (Folder 22.20)
  - Conference on Equal Pay and Equal Opportunity Policy for Women, May 1978 (Folder 22.21)
  - Corporate Governance and the Advancement of Women, 1978-1981 (Folder 22.22)
  - The Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching — Board of Trustees Meeting, Nov 24, 1981 (Folder 22.23)
  - Conference on Educational Environments and the Undergraduate Woman, Sep 1979 (Folder 22.24)
  - AAC — Project Lodestar, 1983 (Folder 22.25)
  - American Council on Education (Correspondence), 1978-1979 (Folder 22.26)
  - American Council on Education — Division Policy Analysis and Research, 1985 (Folder 23.1)
  - AAUW — American Association of University Women, 1980-1982 (Folder 23.2)
  - American Association of University Women, 1985-1988 (Folder 23.3)
  - AAUP — American Association of University Professors (Appeal Procedures), 1984-1987 (Folder 23.4)
  - American Bar Association — Advisory Committee Meeting, 1984 (Folder 23.5)
  - Meeting of the Advisory Commission for College and University Nonprofessional Legal Studies, Nov 5, 1984 (Folder 23.6)
  - ACE (American Council on Education) — Retrospective Report, 1984 (Folder 23.7)
  - American Council on Education, 1982-1985 (Folder 23.8)
  - ACE Annual Meeting — Minneapolis, Oct 1982 (Folder 23.9)
  - ACE — National Committee on Higher Education Issues, Jun 1982 (Folder 23.10)
  - ACE — National Identification Program, 1978-1982 (Folder 23.11)
  - ACE Meeting — San Francisco, 1980 (Folder 23.12)
  - ACE — Coordinating Committee, 1980-1981 (Folder 23.13)
  - ACE Fellows Program, 1981 (Folder 23.14)
  - American Council on Education, 1977-1982 (Folder 23.15)
  - ACE — Intern, 1980 (Folder 23.16)
  - ACE — Freshmen Norms, 1982 (Folder 23.17)
  - ACUSNY (association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York) Meeting, Oct 1980 (Folder 23.18)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1979-1987 (Folder 23.19)
  - AERA (American Education Research Association) — Special Interest Group in Post-Secondary Education, 1978-1979 (Folder 23.20)
  - ACE — Leadership Committee, 1977-1979 (Folder 23.21)
  - Associated Colleges of the Mid-Hudson, 1978-1982 (Folder 23.22)
  - cIcu (Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities) — Tuition Futures Resource Manual, 1987 (Folder 23.23)
  - cIcu Mid-Hudson Regional Meeting at Vassar – Virginia B. Smith Welcome, Oct 1984 (Folder 23.24)
  - cIcu — Long Range Financing Committee, 1978-1981 (Folder 23.25)
  - cIcu — General, 1976-1985 (Folder 23.26)
  - Educational Testing Service (ETS) — Trustees Meeting, Jun 16, 1981 (Folder 24.1)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1979-1981 (Folder 24.2)
  - ETS — Princeton Annual Meeting, Dec 1980 (Folder 24.3)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1979-1982 (Folder 24.4)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1981 (Folder 24.5)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1980 (Folder 24.6)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees, 1979-1981 (Folder 24.7)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 (Folder 24.8)
  - ETS — Full Board Meeting, 1980 (Folder 24.9)
  - ETS — Loose Materials, 1979-1981 (Folder 24.10)
  - ETS — Biographical Files, 1980-1981 (Folder 24.11)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees and Committees (I), 1981 (Folder 24.12)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees and Committees (II), 1981 (Folder 24.13)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees and Committees (III), 1981 (Folder 24.14)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees and Committees, 1980 (Folder 24.15)
  - ETS — Appointment and Mailings, 1979 (Folder 25.1)
  - ETS — VBS Travel Packets for Board Meeting, 1979 (Folder 25.2)
  - ETS — Committee Meetings, 1981 (Folder 25.3)
  - ETS — Research and Development Committee, 1978-1981 (Folder 25.4)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees, 1980-1981 (Folder 25.5)
  - ETS — Board of Trustees Meeting, 1977, 1979 (Folder 25.6)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1979 (Folder 25.7)
  - Educational Testing Service, 1978 (Folder 25.8)
  - ETS — Reports, 1977, 1980 (Folder 25.9)
  - ETS — Committee Meeting, Oct 1979 (Folder 25.10)
  - ETS — Committee on Public Responsibility, Jun 17, 1981 (Folder 25.11)
  - ETS — Testing, 1980-1981 (Folder 25.12)
  - ETS — Executive Committee, May 1981 (Folder 25.13)
  - ETS — Examiner, 1978-1981 (Folder 25.14)
  - ETS — Committee on Finance, 1980-1981 (Folder 25.15)
  - ETS — Presidential Search Committee, 1980 (Folder 25.16)
  - ETS — Executive Committee, 1980-1981 (Folder 25.17)
  - ETS — Audit Committee, Jun 1981 (Folder 25.18)
  - DACOWITS Meeting, 1980 (Folder 25.19)
  - DACOWITS — Loose Materials, 1979-1981 (Folder 25.20)
  - DACOWITS, 1979-1980 (Folder 25.21)
  - Society for Values in Higher Education — Directory, 1981 (Folder 25.22)
- Series VI. Schools and Colleges
  - Secondary Schools — Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Folder 25.23)
  - The Emma Willard School, 1964-1979 (Folder 25.24)
  - Miscellaneous Colleges and Universities — A-I, 1969-1978 (Folder 25.25)
  - Miscellaneous Colleges and Universities — J-Z, 1969-1978 (Folder 25.26)
  - SUNY at New Paltz, 1967-1969 (Folder 25.27)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1976-1978 (Folder 25.28)
  - SUNY — Miscellaneous, 1969-1979 (Folder 25.29)
  - Empire State College — SUNY, 1979 (Folder 25.30)
  - SUNY at Stony Brook, 1976-1979 (Folder 25.31)
  - Sweet Briar, 1980-1981 (Folder 25.32)
  - Miscellaneous Colleges and Universities, 1980-1981 (Folder 26.1)
  - Miscellaneous Colleges and Universities, 1979 (Folder 26.2)
  - Bryn Mawr, 1968-1980 (Folder 26.3)
  - Bard College, 1969-1980 (Folder 26.4)
  - Barnard College, 1973-1981 (Folder 26.5)
  - Bennett College, 1968-1979 (Folder 26.6)
  - University of California, 1968-1979 (Folder 26.7)
  - Colgate University, 1969-1979 (Folder 26.8)
  - Cornell University, 1969-1975 (Folder 26.9)
  - Dartmouth College, 1971-1981 (Folder 26.10)
  - Dutchess Community College, 1968-1980 (Folder 26.11)
  - Elmira College, 1974-1980 (Folder 26.12)
  - Harvard College, 1968-1979 (Folder 26.13)
  - Knox College, 1969-1978 (Folder 26.14)
  - Marist College, 1968-1980 (Folder 26.15)
  - University of Michigan, 1968-1980 (Folder 26.16)
  - Mills College, 1979 (Folder 26.17)
  - Mount Holyoke College, 1969-1982 (Folder 26.18)
  - New York University, 1968-1979 (Folder 26.19)
  - Oberlin College, 1972-1980 (Folder 26.20)
  - Ohio University, 1974 (Folder 26.21)
  - Radcliffe College, 1971-1980 (Folder 26.22)
  - Russell Sage College, 1970-1980 (Folder 26.23)
  - Smith College, 1969-1981 (Folder 26.24)
  - Stanford University, 1969-1981 (Folder 26.25)
  - United States Military Academy, 1971-1980 (Folder 26.26)
  - Wellesley College, 1969-1980 (Folder 26.27)
  - Wheaton College, 1969-1981 (Folder 26.28)
  - Williams College, 1968-1979 (Folder 26.29)
  - Yale University, 1973-1981 (Folder 26.30)
- Series VII. Special Projects
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Centennial Conference — Letters, 1983-1984 (Folder 26.31)
  - Remembrance of Eleanor Roosevelt — Replies, 1984 (Folder 26.32)
  - Governance, 1982; (1 folder) (Folder 26.33)
  - Governance — Computer Printout, 1982 (Folder 26.34)
  - Governance — Loose Materials, 1982 (Folder 26.35)
- Series VIII. General Correspondence
  - Invitations to the President, 1978-1979 (Folder 27.1)
  - Invitations to the President, 1979-1980 (Folder 27.2)
  - Invitations, 1980 (Folder 27.3)
  - Mail Log, 1977 (Folder 27.4)
  - Mail Log, 1978 (Folder 27.5)
  - Mail Log, 1979 (Folder 27.6)
  - Mail Log, 1980 (Folder 27.7)
- Series IX. Additions
  - VBS Retirement, 1986 (Folder 27.8)
  - President’s Seven Year Report, 1977-1982 (Folder 27.9)
  - Coed Study Group, 1983-1984 (Folder 27.10)
  - “Octavia” (Cat), 1980-1981 (Folder 27.11)
  - Friends of Vassar Art Gallery — Board Meeting — Mrs. Laurance Rockefeller, Nov 2, 1984 (Folder 28.1)
  - Audit, 1984 (Folder 28.2)
  - American Association for Higher Education — Assessment Project Lunch Meeting, 1986 (Folder 28.3)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1989-1990 (Folder 28.4)
  - B — General, 1980-1985 (Folder 28.5)
  - [Student] Incident (Confidential), 1987 (Folder 28.6)
  - Dr. Christina Biaggi, 1985 (Folder 28.7)
  - The Before-School Conference — Planning Committee, 1984 (Folder 28.8)
  - Meeting with Dean Sullivan and Mr. Steerman, Sep 14, 1984 (Folder 28.9)
  - Bishop/Brazil, 1986 (Folder 28.10)
  - Blanding, Sarah Gibson — (Gift) Personal, 1976-1987 (Folder 28.11)
  - Blanding Concert, Nov 1985 (Folder 28.12)
  - Deborah Boldt Dinner — Showing of “Miles to Go”, Nov 1984 (Folder 28.13)
  - Fred R. Brooks, 1983-1985 (Folder 28.14)
  - Barbara Bailey Brown Symposium, 1983-1984 (Folder 28.15)
  - Barbara Bailey Brown Lecture, 1982-1983 (Folder 28.16)
  - Barbara Bailey Brown Lecture, 1981-1982 (Folder 28.17)
  - Barbara Bailey Brown Lecture, 1980 (Folder 28.18)
  - Barbara Bailey Brown Reception, 1980 (Folder 28.19)
  - Barbara Bailey Brown Lecture, 1979-1980 (Folder 28.20)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Folder 28.21)
  - Budget, 1984-1985 (Folder 28.22)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Folder 28.23)
  - Budget, 1982-1983 (Folder 28.24)
  - Budget, 1981-1982 (Folder 28.25)
  - Budget, 1980-1981 (Folder 28.26)
  - Budget (Correspondence), 1980-1981; (1 folder) (Folder 28.27)
  - Budget/Contingency Funds, 1980-1981 (Folder 28.28)
  - Budget — President’s Discretionary, 1981 (Folder 28.29)
  - Budget — Long Range Financial Information, 1980 (Folder 28.30)
  - John Burroughs Day, Apr 21, 1983 (Folder 28.31)
  - Burroughs’ Journals, 1980-1982 (Folder 28.32)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1982-1983 (Folder 28.33)
  - Peter Rainey, 1984-1987 (Folder 28.34)
  - Executive Director of Career Development, 1983 (Folder 28.35)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 1984-1985 (Folder 28.36)
  - Christmas Cards, 1985 (Folder 28.37)
  - Christmas Cards, 1984 (Folder 28.38)
  - Christmas Cards — Listings/Additions, 1981 (Folder 28.39)
  - Clark/Warren Visit, 1982-1984 (Folder 28.40)
  - Coalition of College Presidents for Civic Responsibility, Jan 1986 (Folder 28.41)
  - College bowl, 1984 (Folder 28.42)
  - College Course, 1984-1986 (Folder 28.43)
  - Community Day, 1983 (Folder 28.44)
  - Community Tension, 1983 (Folder 28.45)
  - Office of the Comptroller, 1980-1986 (Folder 28.46)
  - Sidney Borthwick, Comptroller, 1982-1987 (Folder 28.47)
  - H. Patrick Sullivan, Dean, 1985-1986 (Folder 28.48)
  - Double Image Theater, 1985-1986 (Folder 28.49)
  - Double Image Theater — Correspondence, 1986 (Folder 28.50)
  - Department Chairs, 1984 (Folder 28.51)
  - Dean of the College Office, 1985-1989 (Folder 28.52)
  - Drug Arrest, 1985 (Folder 28.53)
  - Drugs (Folder 28.54)
  - Early Retirement, 1984 (Folder 28.55)
  - Early Retirement, 1979-1986 (Folder 28.56)
  - Early Retirement Plans, 1979-1981 (Folder 29.1)
  - Faculty Exchange, 1983-1984 (Folder 29.2)
  - Faculty — Promotions and Reappointments, 1983-1987 (Folder 29.3)
  - Faculty Reviews — A Brief Account, 1982-1985 (Folder 29.4)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology Meeting, Dec 10, 1985 (Folder 29.5)
  - Financial Equilibrium Study, 1981 (Folder 29.6)
  - Edward Fiske Visit, 1984-1986 (Folder 29.7)
  - “Genius”, 1987 (Folder 29.8)
  - John Gleason, 1987 (Folder 29.9)
  - Goodfellowship Club House (Folder 29.10)
  - Molly Halsten, 1980-1982 (Folder 29.11)
  - Higher Education Resource Services (HERS) Regional Meeting, 1985 (Folder 29.12)
  - HERS, 1986-1987 (Folder 29.13)
  - HERS Presentation, Jul 28, 1986 (Folder 29.14)
  - HERS — Women in Public Leadership — Planning Meeting, 1981-1984 (Folder 29.15)
  - Higher Education — Meeting Training/Conference, 1984-1986 (Folder 29.16)
  - Board of House Presidents, 1984-1985 (Folder 29.17)
  - Hunger Symposium, 1985-1986 (Folder 29.18)
  - International Center for Educational Advancement, 1986 (Folder 29.19)
  - International Studies, 1983-1986 (Folder 29.20)
  - Invitations to the President, 1988 (Folder 29.21)
  - Program for Jesse Jackson, 1984 (Folder 29.22)
  - Kresge Foundation Grant, 1984-1985 (Folder 29.23)
  - “Kudos”, 1983-1985 (Folder 29.24)
  - Library/Papers, 1981-1987 (Folder 29.25)
  - Library, 1980-1987 (Folder 29.26)
  - Automated System, 1987-1988 (Folder 29.27)
  - Status of Librarians, 1982 (Folder 29.28)
  - Library Proposal — “Research Methods with Manuscripts”, 1981 (Folder 29.29)
  - Ed Linner and Matthew Vassar Biography, 1983-1984 (Folder 29.30)
  - Visit of Jamaican Former Prime Minister Michael Manley, 1986 (Folder 29.31)
  - Matthew Club Reading Group, 1985-1987 (Folder 29.32)
  - Mellon Chair in Art, 1984 (Folder 29.33)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer News (Debate between Smith and Solomon), 1984 (Folder 29.34)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1984-1985 (Folder 29.35)
  - Nancy Milford/Biog’s Art, 1982-1983 (Folder 29.36)
  - Judith Moyers — Exxon, 1984 (Folder 29.37)
  - Mudd Chemistry Building Dedication, Oct 1984 (Folder 29.38)
  - Mudd Symposium, Sep 1985 (Folder 29.39)
  - Mudd Chemistry Building — Reports, 1981-1988 (Folder 29.40)
  - National Science Foundation — Research in Undergraduate Institutes, 1983-1986 (Folder 29.41)
  - National Women’s Conference on Preventing nuclear War, 1984 (Folder 29.42)
  - New York State Review, 1982-1984 (Folder 29.43)
  - New York State HEDS-HEGIS, 1983 (Folder 29.44)
  - New York State Education Department — General, 1981-1985 (Folder 29.45)
  - New York State Education Department — Master Plan — Vassar College, 1976-1979 (Folder 29.46)
  - Peat-Marwick-Mitchell Co., 1978-1984 (Folder 29.47)
  - Parking, 1987 (Folder 29.48)
  - Personnel Matters, 1981-1988 (Folder 29.49)
  - Personnel Requests, 1985-1986 (Folder 29.50)
  - President’s Portraits, 1986 (Folder 29.51)
  - Poughkeepsie Day School, 1984 (Folder 19.52)
  - Presidential Search Committee (1), 1985 (Folder 29.53)
  - Presidential Search Committee (2), 1985-1986 (Folder 29.54)
  - President’s Advisory Group, 1984-1985 (Folder 30.1)
  - President’s Advisory Group, 1984-1985 (Folder 30.2)
  - PAG Questions, 1984 (Folder 30.3)
  - President’s Entertainment, 1985-1986 (Folder 30.4)
  - Recommendations by VBS (Student, Faculty, Administrative), 1980-1985 (Folder 30.5)
  - Smith Retirement Dinner, 1986 (Folder 30.6)
  - SOS, 1986 (Folder 30.7)
  - Speeches (VBS) — Chamber of Commerce, 1981 (Folder 30.8)
  - Seven College Conference, 1983 (Folder 30.9)
  - Soviet Jewry Program, 1985 (Folder 30.10)
  - Freshman Parents Weekend, 1987 (Folder 30.11)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, Apr 1986 (Folder 30.12)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, 1985 (Folder 30.13)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, Apr 1984 (Folder 30.14)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, Apr 1983 (Folder 30.15)
  - Sophomore Parents’ Weekend, 1981 (Folder 30.16)
  - Student Leadership Retreat, 1985-1986 (Folder 30.17)
  - Fritzi Horstman ’84 — Senior Class President, 1983 (Folder 30.18)
  - Special Students, 1982-1989 (Folder 30.19)
  - [Student] Appeal (Confidential), 1989 (Folder 30.20)
  - Student Aid (Folder 30.21)
  - Student Credit Union, 1985-1986 (Folder 30.22)
  - Vassar Asian Students Association, 1980 (Folder 30.23)
  - Vassar Debate Society, 1986-1987 (Folder 30.24)
  - Students — Returning Student Association (Folder 30.25)
  - VSA President, 1985-1989 (Folder 30.26)
  - [Student] (Highly Confidential), 1989 (Folder 30.27)
  - Vassar Student Association, 1986-1987 (Folder 30.28)
  - Daniel Rosenthal ’90, 1989 (Folder 30.29)
  - Vassar Student Association — General, 1983-1988 (Folder 30.30)
  - TAP, 1984 (Folder 30.31)
  - Task Force on Teaching, 1981-1984 (Folder 30.32)
  - Tax Law Implications, 1984-1985 (Folder 30.33)
  - Tuition Increase Letter, Feb 1986 (Folder 30.34)
  - Tuition Increase, 1985 (Folder 30.35)
  - Tuition Increase Letter, Feb 1984 (Folder 30.36)
  - TIAA/CREF, 1985-1987 (Folder 30.37)
  - TIAA/CREF, 1981-1984 (Folder 30.38)
  - Tuition Increase Letter, Feb 1983 (Folder 30.39)
  - Tuition Increase, 1982 (Folder 30.40)
  - Tuition Increase, 1981 (Folder 30.41)
  - Tuition — Financial Aid Letter, Feb 1982 (Folder 30.42)
  - Vassar Quarterly, 1985-1987 (Folder 30.43)
  - Vassar Quarterly — The Inauguration of the President, 1978, 1986 (Folder 30.44)
  - Vassar Quarterly — Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Folder 30.45)
  - Vassar Today, 1985 (Folder 30.46)
  - Vassar Today Dinner, Oct 1984 (Folder 30.47)
  - Vassar Today, Apr 1984 (Folder 30.48)
  - Vassar Views, 1984-1987 (Folder 30.49)
  - Vassar Today, Oct 1983 (Folder 30.50)
  - Vassar Today, 1980 (Folder 30.50a)
  - Vassar Today, 1981 Oct 2 (Folder 30.50b)
  - Vassar Today, 1981 (Folder 30.50c)
  - Vassar Today, 1982 (Folder 30.50d)
  - Vassar Today, Spring 1983 (Folder 30.50e)
  - Weird, 1989 (Folder 30.51)
  - W — General, 1979-1985 (Folder 30.52)
  - WVKR Interview, 1985 (Folder 30.53)
  - White house Fellow, 1985 (Folder 30.54)
  - Wellesley — The Stone Center, 1981 (Folder 30.55)
  - AAVC — Class Letters, Dec 1985 (Folder 30.56)
  - AAVC — Fund, 1983-1986 (Folder 30.57)
  - AAVC Fund Workshop, 1984-1986 (Folder 30.58)
  - Mary Gesek, 1983-1988 (Folder 30.59)
  - AAVC — Letters from Class Representatives, 1984 (Folder 30.60)
  - AAVC — General, 1983-1989 (Folder 30.61)
  - Alumnae House, 1980-1986 (Folder 30.62)
  - AAVC — College Coordination, 1984 (Folder 30.63)
  - AAVC Council, 1984-1985 (Folder 31.1)
  - Coordinating Council, Apr 1986 (Folder 31.2)
  - AAVC — Club Presidents and Admission Representatives, 1987-1988 (Folder 31.3)
  - AAVC — Class of 1986 (Folder 31.4)
  - V.C. Board Nominations, 1984-1987 (Folder 31.5)
  - AAVC Fall Council, 1987 (Folder 31.6)
  - AAVC, 1986 (Folder 31.7)
  - Reunions, 1988 (Folder 31.8)
  - Reunions, 1987 (Folder 31.9)
  - Reunions, 1987-1988; (1 folder) (Folder 31.10)
  - Reunion Weekend, May 1987 (Folder 31.11)
  - Reunion, 1987 (Folder 31.12)
  - AAVC (Travel/Trips), 1983-1986 (Folder 31.13)
  - AAVC Assistant for Recent Classes — Donna M. Walker, 1984 (Folder 31.14)
  - Frannie Hess, 1986-1987 (Folder 31.15)
  - Alumnae/i Impressions of Vassar Today, 1983 (Folder 31.16)
  - Development/AAVC Fund Workshop Questionnaires, 1984 (Folder 31.17)
  - Preliminary Program for Black Alumnae/I Forum, Apr 1984 (Folder 31.18)
  - Employee Addresses, 1988 (Folder 31.19)